[
  {
    "userId": 7752047213,
    "name": "Diyorbek Musulmonov",
    "question": "1.IAKT fani o'zi nima?",
    "answer": "adasdasd",
    "timestamp": "2025-10-21T20:20:02.853Z"
  },
  {
    "userId": 7752047213,
    "name": "Diyorbek Musulmonov",
    "question": "1.IAKT fani o'zi nima?",
    "answer": "dfsdfsdfsdfsf",
    "timestamp": "2025-10-21T20:21:13.487Z"
  },
  {
    "userId": 7752047213,
    "name": "Diyorbek Musulmonov",
    "question": "1.IAKT fani o'zi nima?",
    "answer": "12312314fasfasfvss",
    "timestamp": "2025-10-21T20:30:49.185Z"
  },
  {
    "userId": 7752047213,
    "name": "Diyorbek Musulmonov",
    "question": "1.IAKT fani o'zi nima?",
    "answer": "asdAFASFaG",
    "timestamp": "2025-10-21T20:37:30.391Z"
  },
  {
    "userId": 7752047213,
    "name": "Diyorbek Musulmonov",
    "question": "1.IAKT fani o'zi nima?",
    "answer": "dasfas",
    "timestamp": "2025-10-21T20:38:03.981Z"
  },
  {
    "userId": 1987420383,
    "name": "Musulmonov Diyorbek",
    "question": "1.IAKT fani o'zi nima?",
    "answer": "sasfasdf",
    "timestamp": "2025-10-21T20:42:17.730Z"
  },
  {
    "userId": 1987420383,
    "name": "Musulmonov Diyorbek",
    "question": "1.IAKT fani o'zi nima?",
    "answer": "sdasdasd",
    "timestamp": "2025-10-21T20:46:18.369Z"
  },
  {
    "userId": 7752047213,
    "name": "Diyorbek Musulmonov",
    "question": "1.IAKT fani o'zi nima?",
    "answer": "dasdasd",
    "timestamp": "2025-10-21T20:46:40.519Z"
  },
  {
    "userId": 7752047213,
    "name": "Diyorbek Musulmonov",
    "question": "1.IAKT fani o'zi nima?",
    "answer": "asfdasfa",
    "timestamp": "2025-10-21T20:50:30.670Z"
  },
  {
    "userId": 7752047213,
    "name": "Diyorbek Musulmonov",
    "question": "1 nimagaunday?",
    "answer": "hfghgfhfghfgh",
    "timestamp": "2025-10-21T20:52:03.641Z"
  },
  {
    "userId": 7752047213,
    "name": "Diyorbek Musulmonov",
    "question": "1 nimagaunday?",
    "answer": "dasdasd",
    "timestamp": "2025-10-21T20:56:46.280Z"
  },
  {
    "userId": 7752047213,
    "name": "Diyorbek Musulmonov",
    "question": "1 nimagaunday?",
    "answer": "dasfasfasf",
    "timestamp": "2025-10-21T20:59:56.700Z"
  },
  {
    "userId": 7752047213,
    "name": "Diyorbek Musulmonov",
    "question": "1 nimagaunday?",
    "answer": "dasdasda",
    "timestamp": "2025-10-21T21:04:28.258Z"
  },
  {
    "userId": 7752047213,
    "name": "Diyorbek Musulmonov",
    "question": "1 nimagaunday?",
    "answer": "wrqwrqwr",
    "timestamp": "2025-10-21T21:09:06.366Z"
  },
  {
    "userId": 7752047213,
    "name": "Diyorbek Musulmonov",
    "question": "2 asfasfsdgsdg?",
    "answer": "rqwrqwrqwr",
    "timestamp": "2025-10-21T21:09:12.715Z"
  },
  {
    "userId": 7752047213,
    "name": "Diyorbek Musulmonov",
    "question": "3dfsdgfsdgg?",
    "answer": "rqwrqwrqwrrqwrqwr",
    "timestamp": "2025-10-21T21:09:18.035Z"
  },
  {
    "userId": 7752047213,
    "name": "Diyorbek Musulmonov",
    "question": "4 dsfagafdgsdfg?",
    "answer": "rqwrqwrqwrqwrqwrqwrqwrqwrqwrqwrqwrqwrqwrqwr",
    "timestamp": "2025-10-21T21:09:26.880Z"
  }
]